http://www.skycreek.com/privacy-policy/

Support - 855-SKYCREEK(759-2733)LoginDemoToggle navigationSolutionsAppointment RemindersPre-Dispatch Confirms and CancelsPreemptive Service NotificationsPost-Interaction Employee Performance SurveysOrder VerificationsCustomer Compliance VerificationsSentiment Surveys & AnalysisFollow-up Contact ComplianceCustom Multi-Channel SolutionsProductseContacteTouchPointIndustriesTelecom & CableFinancial ServicesRetail & TravelInsuranceUtilitiesGovernmentServicesRedundant Solution Hosting InfrastructureCustom IVR/SMS/Email SolutionsCustomer TranscriptionsProfessional Services
& Enterprise IntegrationResourcesBlogCompanyAboutSkyCreek ManagementContact SkyCreekPartnersSupportEnterpriseMulti-ChannelContact MGMTPrivacy PolicySkyCreek values protection of your privacy and personal data. To ensure a high level of transparency and security, our declaration on data protection as set forth below will inform you as to the nature, scope and purpose of any collection, use and processing of information provided by users via our website.1) External LinksAny reference to third parties on our website or links to third parties from our website are not governed by the SkyCreek Privacy Policy. SkyCreek has no influence whatsoever on the contents and design of sites of other providers and therefore cannot extend the warranties under this declaration on data protection to such sites.2) CookiesA cookie is a small data text file stored on your computer or mobile device (if permitted by your browser) that SkyCreek can retrieve to identify you while you are on our site. The cookies can only be read by the website which set it. No other company has access to these cookies. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or device, pass on a computer virus, or capture your email address.It is possible for you to set your browser so cookies are rejected or you are informed of them before they’re stored. Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects (LSO), session storage or DOM are not used by SkyCreek.Our website may use so-called session cookies. These cookies deposit data for purposes of technical regulation in your browser’s memory. However, they do not contain any personal data and are deleted after your browser is closed.SkyCreek deposits mandatory cookies on your computer, which are partly not deleted after conclusion of your session. This makes it possible for the website to recognize your computer at your next visit and adapt the website to your interests. With your consent, SkyCreek stores your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time. Mandatory cookies are also used for the limited purpose of optimizing and personalizing your website experience.3) Communication and Use Related Data Generally speaking, you may visit SkyCreek’s website without us finding out who you are. Only for statistical and internal system-related purposes do we record the access time, the quantity of data transferred, the pages of ours that you visited, the page from which you accessed our website and the browser that you use (log files), in addition to your IP address. To the extent that such information might enable conclusions in relation to personal data, these are subject to the relevant statutory data protection provisions. The data is not personalized and is deleted following statistical evaluation.4) Collecting Personal DataIn order to be able to utilize the services offered on our website, in particular, individual enquiries, registrations for white papers or registrations for other services, it is necessary that we obtain personal data from you. The personal data entails individual statements concerning personal and material relations pertaining to you, such as your name, your address, your phone number or your e-mail address. Such information is collected by us only if you provide it voluntarily and show us in this way that you agree to the use and processing thereof. In this respect, it goes without saying for us that such data is necessarily only collected where it is absolutely mandatory for the implementation of relevant offers. Where we request additional data, this occurs solely for purposes of, for example, facilitating communication with you or improving our service.5) Use of Personal DataSkyCreek uses and processes the personal data provided for purposes of processing your enquiries and requests. Data with personal content is processed and used to a limited extent for customer management and marketing purposes, provided the relevant statutory provisions permit this. Should you no longer agree to such use, you may, of course, object to further use at any time.Moreover, your information provided to us may be combined with data on you that has already been stored by us. Such data combination has, among other things, the advantage of keeping your data collected by us updated at all times, guaranteeing the accuracy of the collected information and being able to optimize our service to you.We use and process your data outside these parameters only if you have expressly granted your prior consent thereto and only for purposes of which you have been advised.6) Forwarding of DataIn order to better facilitate your interaction with SkyCreek, it might be necessary to forward data entered by you to one of our employees or office locations.  Such transmission takes place only within our company and only for the aforementioned purposes.We do not forward your data to other third parties, unless we are obliged to do so by virtue of statutory provisions or judicial order.  In particular, your personal data shall not be sold, leased or exchanged.7) E-mail Contact Should you provide us with your e-mail address, we will also communicate with you by e-mail. Should you no longer desire such information, you may at any time to revoke your consent. In this case, please send us a short message to the e-mail address admin@skycreek.com.8) Data Protection for MinorsThe information and offers on this website are not directed at children. We therefore assume that we will not become aware of any personal data pertaining to children.9) Technical and Organizational Data Protection SkyCreek takes the technical and organizational measures necessary to protect the information provided by you against abuse and loss. Such data is stored in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to the public. In addition, each of our employees is instructed on data protection and obliged to enter into confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements.10) E-Mails to SkyCreekThe e-mail system of SkyCreek and other members of the SkyCreek corporate family are intended to be used for business purposes only.11) Modification of our Privacy PolicyAs a result of ongoing technical development activities, it may be necessary to adapt this privacy policy to changing conditions on an ongoing basis. Timely notice of such modification shall be given on this page.12) Information and ContactUpon written request, our security officer will provide you with information as to whether – and if so, which – personal data we store in relation to you. Should your personal data be incorrect, you may have this rectified by informing SkyCreek of the error and requesting the error be fixed. Any such information or modification is free of charge.Moreover, you are entitled to revoke your consent to use of your personal data in the future, in whole or in part. Should you desire this, we will delete or block your relevant data.  In order to assert such rights, please contact SkyCreek’s security officer. You may contact SkyCreek’s security officer directly at any time should you have questions, comments or complaints in connection with this declaration on data protection:SkyCreek Security Officer E-mail: joe_enrico@skycreek.com × Success!Thank you for requesting more information. A SkyCreek representative will contact you shortly × Error! Please retry your submission again Contact us today for a demo of our advanced multi-channel Privacy Policy.
About SkycreekSkyCreek, professionally designs and manages custom multi-channel (IVR, Email, SMS) customer contact and experience management solutions. We optimize the cost-efficiency, experience quality, and operational performance of front-line customer-employee interactions for some of the largest national service providers and contact operations in North America. Our goal is to help companies elevate their use of customer contact technologies to attain breakthroughs in operational cost containment, customer satisfaction and service differentiation.We do this by bringing together:20 years of customer contact management experience in Fortune 500 service providersHardened, scalable, and advanced multi-channel (IVR, Email, SMS) contact technologiesIndustry best practice contact strategies, interaction designs, messages and techniquesEnterprise solution development and integration servicesVeteran dedicated contact program management and supportA flexible partnership approach in working with customersWe host our solutions on our eContact and eTouchPoint platforms, residing on a fully-redundant, scalable, SSAE-16 compliant, geographically-dispersed service infrastructure with data centers in Reston, Chicago, Dallas and San Diego.Socialize With UsWhat we doOur SolutionsAppointment RemindersPre-Dispatch Confirms and CancelsPreemptive Service NotificationsPost-Interaction Employee Performance SurveysOrder VerificationsCustomer Compliance VerificationsSentiment Surveys & AnalysisFollow-up Contact ComplianceCustom Multi-Channel SolutionsContact SkyCreek
Name * Your Email (required) Your Message
×Request SkyCreek Demo
Name * Name * Name * Your Email (required) Your Message
Contact us for a demo of any of SkyCreek’s multi-channel customer contact technologies
